



I am currently working as a Senior Developer Level 2/Tech Lead in the Gaming Industry. I gained my master's degree in computer science in 2007. Worked as full stack developer from 2007 to 2009 by building intelligent building management systems with C++ and SQL. In 2009, I joined the gaming industry, became a front-end developer working on C++, ActionScript, JavaScript, and typescript. I created my first game engine in 2012, which became one of the most successful and long-standing game engines in our company. More than a hundred games have been developed on this engine, including many of our company's legendary games. This engine is still in use today in 2022. Since 2019, I have been working on a new game engine focused on fast development and maintainability. For fast delivery, we build our engine on top of Cocos Creator to utilize its UI Editing and templating capability. For maintainability, we focus on re-usability, unit testing and automation, aiming to use a single code base to drive a large number of games. Currently, the entire department is adopting this new engine. For some of our games, we are able to reduce our development time from 3 months to a week.

EXPERIENCE

SENIOR DEVELOPER LEVEL 2/TECH LEAD **▼ GAMES GLOBAL** since Sep 2021, Guiding the technical direction and architecture design of game engine. Leading a group of Develops design/develop components, data layer, automation.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER **▼ COMPANY B** January 2015 - December 2015 , Fulfillment of extremely important tasks.

TRAINEE **▼ COMPANY C**March 2014 - December 2014 , Making coffee and baking cookies.

EDUCATION

MASTER OF ARTS

Major in Hacking and Computer Penetration, University A, New York, USA.

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE

Major in Engineering, University B, Los Angeles, USA.

SKILLS

> JavaScript/TypeScript

MongoDB

> Vue

> SQL

Cypress

> Node.js

> (#/(++

Specializing in Game Engine development. Proficient in software architecure design. Fluent in English and Chinese.

CONTACT

wilson96wu@gmail.com; +27 725716932; , Durban, South Africa; https://wilson96wu.github.io/cv/;